{
    "1": {"question": "In primitive times, barbers were once known as what and what services did they perform?", "answer": "Barber surgeons, dentistry, minor surgery and bloodletting"},
    "2": {"question": "What do the colors of the barber pole symbolize?", "answer": "Red = blood, white = bandages, blue = veins"},
    "3": {"question": "Who created the first barber school and where was it located?", "answer": "1893A.B. by Moler in Chicago"},
    "4": {"question": "Where and when was the first state barber law created?", "answer": "1897 in Minnesota"},
    "5": {"question": "There are 2 types of bacteria, what are they called and what is the difference between them?", "answer": "Pathogenic bacteria will hurt you and NON-Pathogenic will NOT hurt you"},
    "6": {"question": "What is the purpose of the State Barber Board?", "answer": "Protect the health, safety, and welfare of the public"},
    "7": {"question": "What are the 3 types of pathogenic bacteria?", "answer": "Bacilli, spirilla, and cocci"},
    "8": {"question": "Besides dying off, what are the other 2 stages of bacteria?", "answer": "Active, inactive, and dead"},
    "9": {"question": "What is a characteristic of each of the different types of bacteria?", "answer": "Pathogenic bacteria will hurt you and NON-Pathogenic will NOT hurt you"},
    "10": {"question": "What is the scientific name for lice?", "answer": "Pediculosis, louse"},
    "11": {"question": "What is the technical term for ringworm?", "answer": "Tinea"},
    "12": {"question": "Many people catching the same illness in a small area is called what?", "answer": "Epidemic"},
    "13": {"question": "What are the 2 different types of infections and what is the difference?", "answer": "General (spread all over the body) and local (found in one spot)"},
    "14": {"question": "What is the highest level of decontamination you would use in the barbershop?", "answer": "Disinfection"},
    "15": {"question": "What is the difference between antiseptics and disinfectants?", "answer": "Antiseptics are used on the skin, disinfectants are used on clippers, barber chairs, and countertops"}
}

